[
    {
      "question": "What is the mode of these numbers:<br> [1, 1, 2, 4, 1, 5, 1, 3]?",
      "correctAnswer": "1",
      "options": [
        "0",
        "1",
        "2",
        "3"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mode of these numbers:<br> [4, 2, 2, 2, 2, 6, 3, 5, 2]?",
      "correctAnswer": "2",
      "options": [
        "1",
        "2",
        "3",
        "4"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mode of these numbers:<br> [3, 7, 5, 4, 6, 6, 6]?",
      "correctAnswer": "6",
      "options": [
        "5",
        "6",
        "7",
        "8"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mode of these numbers:<br> [4, 4, 4, 7, 4, 8, 6, 5]?",
      "correctAnswer": "4",
      "options": [
        "3",
        "4",
        "5",
        "6"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mode of these numbers:<br> [9, 5, 6, 8, 7, 8, 8, 8, 8]?",
      "correctAnswer": "8",
      "options": [
        "7",
        "8",
        "9",
        "10"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mode of these numbers:<br> [10, 7, 9, 7, 6, 8, 7]?",
      "correctAnswer": "7",
      "options": [
        "6",
        "7",
        "8",
        "9"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mode of these numbers:<br> [11, 8, 10, 7, 8, 8, 8, 9]?",
      "correctAnswer": "8",
      "options": [
        "7",
        "8",
        "9",
        "10"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mode of these numbers:<br> [12, 10, 9, 11, 12, 12, 12, 8, 12]?",
      "correctAnswer": "12",
      "options": [
        "11",
        "12",
        "13",
        "14"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mode of these numbers:<br> [12, 11, 13, 9, 11, 11, 10]?",
      "correctAnswer": "11",
      "options": [
        "10",
        "11",
        "12",
        "13"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mode of these numbers:<br> [14, 14, 11, 14, 12, 10, 13, 14]?",
      "correctAnswer": "14",
      "options": [
        "13",
        "14",
        "15",
        "16"
      ]
    }
]